<Concepts>
<!-- #The Old Realms -->
  <Concept title="{=!}Blood Kiss" id="str_tor_bloodkiss" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_BLOODKISS" text=
"The Blood Kiss is a mechanic that allows human characters to be turned into a {TOR_VAMPIRE}, bringing with it all the benefits and detriments of the transformation.{newline}
{newline}To receive the Blood Kiss you must join a Vampire faction and once you reach Clan Level 4 speak to its faction leader - Walach Harkon for Blood Knights or Mannfred von Carstein for Vampire Nobility."/>
  <Concept title="{=!}Character Creation" id="str_tor_charactercreation" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_CHARACTERCREATION" text=
"Vampires{newline}If you wish to start the game as a Vampire, you must choose the ‘Vampire Nobility’ option during character creation, this should be your final choice before loading into the campaign map. It will allow to choose your Blood Line. You either become a Vampire Noble or start your adventure as a Blood Knight. {newline}
{newline}Being a Vampire provides a unique set of bonuses and abilities, from the very start of your playthrough: You gain the ability to raise the dead, you can move faster at night and you are more agile than humans.
{newline}Note that you also will be facing some disadvantages, for example slower travel speed during the day. As a Vampire you will start your playthrough hated by the Empire and most other living factions.{newline}
{newline}Necromancers
{newline}If you wish to start the game as a necromancer, you must choose the Novice Necromancer option during character creation - this should be one of the final options given to you. Once selected you will load into the map with access to Necromancy magic and the ability to raise the dead after battles to supplement your army.{newline}
{newline}Wizards and Magic Users
{newline}To start the game as a wizard, and this applies to most factions, you must select the correct final option during character creation, which will contain ‘allows for the use of magic’ in the description.{newline}
{newline}For example within the Empire, choose to be a College Acolyte upon game start and you will load into the game with access to magic. Once loaded into the campaign map a prompt will let you choose the lore of magic you wish to specialise in. From this point onward you are free to play the campaign as normal with access to a number of starting spells. Remember you CANNOT learn more than one lore of magic as a human (unless you are a Damsel, see {TOR_CAREERS}).{newline}
{newline}Priests and Damsels of the Lady
{newline}Priest careers can be selected upon starting the game. They provide powerful battle prayers (see {TOR_PRAYERS}). 
{newline}
{newline}Knights Errant
{newline}The Knight of Bretonnia is one of the unique {TOR_CAREERS} you can start with when playing as Bretonnia.{newline}
{newline}Standard options
{newline}Choosing any other career start for your campaign will result in a similar experience as vanilla Bannerlord - you will load into the game with gear based on your choice and the freedom to make your own story from scratch. When no career is chosen at the beginning, you will instead start with the Mercenary career which provides various bonuses (see {TOR_CAREERS}).{newline}
{newline}
{newline}
"/>
  <Concept title="{=!}Careers" id="str_tor_careers" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_CAREERS" text=
  "Careers are a system you can engage with for both roleplaying and character development, providing unique skills and bonuses depending on your specialization. These Careers are similar to skill trees that require specific feats to be achieved to allow progression, which can include additional health points, increased damage, or party buffs related to the career in question.{newline}
  {newline}Skill Points, which are used to advance through a Career, are acquired by leveling up with the base Bannerlord system. For every level your character gains one Career point.{newline}
  {newline}Within a playthrough you are supposed to specialise in a single career choice; however there will be an option to change between careers but not without penalties, such as losing all your progress and abilities earned. You will have your skill points returned to you so that you can advance in your new career choice.{newline}
  {newline}Note: Switching careers may of course result in the loss of magic, prayers or abilities that can reduce your overall battle strength. In the current state switching is only possible by receiving a {TOR_BLOODKISS} as Mercenary.{newline}
  {newline}The current Career skill trees in the mod include Grail Knight, Blood Knight, Warrior Priest, Mercenary, Vampire Nobility and the Damsel. Each accompanied with their own unique and appropriately themed progression via their unique Career Skill tree found on the Character screen, in the upper right corner.{newline}
  {newline}Every career is divided into 3 ranks, each allowing you to pick special perks. The benefits of these perks vary from simple passive buffs to more advanced and unique benefits for the specific career.{newline}
  {newline}Career Abilities
  {newline}Some careers have a specific career ability. Career abilities allow for unique temporary combat buffs or unique action skills like turning into mist as a Vampire.{newline}
  {newline}
  {newline}
  Base Career: 
  {newline}
  {newline}
  Mercenary{newline}
  - Melee and ranged combat bonuses{newline}
  - Can earn extra gold from certain enemies and contracts{newline}
  - Bonuses for different troops{newline}
  {newline}
  {newline}
  Empire: {newline}
  {newline}
  Warrior Priest of Sigmar{newline}
  - Gains access to buffs and some damaging abilities {newline}
  - Melee fighter with powerful survival skills{newline}
  - Bonuses to all Simgarite units{newline}
  {newline}
  {newline}
  Bretonnia: {newline}
  {newline}
  Knight of Bretonnia{newline}
  - Focus on mounted combat and charging into the fray{newline}
  - Holy and physical damage types{newline}
  - Bonuses for horses and knight units{newline}
  {newline}
  Damsel of the Lady{newline}
  - Gains access to both spells and prayers{newline}
  - Bonuses and buffs for Bretonnian troops {newline}
  - Unlocks three schools of magic{newline}
  {newline}
  {newline}
  Vampire Counts:{newline}
  {newline}
  Vampire Nobility{newline}
  - The ability to fly during battle via the Mistform ability{newline}
  - Gains access to Necromancy{newline}
  - Can learn two lores of magic{newline}
  {newline}
  Blood Knight{newline}
  - No access to magic but very powerful in melee, with a large health pool{newline}
  - Gains the ability to convert worthy opponents into Blood Knight units{newline}
  - Armour penetrating attacks in the late game{newline}
   {newline}
   {newline}
  " />
  
  <Concept title="{=!}Companions" id="str_tor_companions" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_COMPANIONS" text=
  "Companions within our mod have been changed to better suit our setting; however, at this time the recruitment and interaction with these companion NPCs remain primarily unchanged. They are found in taverns and recruited with a single payment, just like vanilla Bannerlord.{newline}
  {newline}Similarily to the vanilla experience, these companions are generic and differ in equipment, but can specialize in custom skills and special abilities such as access to magic or prayers, which only the relevant companion type will have.{newline}
  {newline}The one notable difference are faction-specific companions, such as Vampires, which can be found solely in their appropriate territory. For example Vampire companions being found in Sylvanian taverns and Warrior Priests within the Empire.{newline}
  {newline}The companion types include Warrior Priests, Knights, Wizards, Vampires and more.{newline}" />
  
  <Concept title="{=!}Cursed Locations" id="str_tor_cursed_locations" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_CURSEDLOCATIONS" text=
  "As a Vampire or necromancer, you can interact with certain cursed locations on the campaign map. These will allow you to summon undead units but the ritual can only be performed once a day. Cursed locations can be found within but are not limited to the swamps of Sylvania or Mousillon. This blighted land will cause attrition (damage to troops and characters) to the travelling party and healing won’t be possible until the area has been left. Over time these negative effects will grow stronger.{newline}
  {newline}As a non-Vampire or necromancer character, you can interact with these locations in a different way by conducting a warding ritual. This ritual will temporarily stop the recruitment of undead units by undead factions and remove the negative penalties for the player and any non-undead factions. To perform this ritual your party must have at lest 9 units and some will take damage during the process.{newline}
  {newline}" />
	
  <Concept title="{=!}Damage System" id="str_tor_damagesystem" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_DAMAGESYSTEM" text=
  "We have implemented our own damage system, which takes into account a variety of factors during battles - unit types and the damage or resistance modifiers being used by individual characters. The damage system works within the base Bannerlord physics-based damage system. A mighty well-timed blow will be further enhanced by magical and other non-physical effects. On the other hand units with physical resistance, like ethereal units, take less damage from non-magic weapons.{newline}
  {newline}Damage types{newline}
  - Physical: regular damage dealt from the vast majority of weapons and some spells. {newline}
  - Magical: some artifact weapons and most spells deal magical damage. {newline}
  - Fire: dealt by special guns and most Bright magic spells. {newline}
  - Holy: dealt by most prayers or even certain holy weapons.{newline}
  - Lightning: Heavens wizards and higher level Damsels make use of this damage type.{newline}
	{newline}Damage proportions
{newline}If a certain weapon or unit type possesses non-physical damage effects, their damage can be split into categories. For example spells deal full damage, aligned to the element of the magic in use.{newline}
	{newline}Buffs, debuffs and resistances
	{newline}Certain magical gear or abilities can enhance damage dealt, reduce damage taken or enhance a particular damage type. In a playthrough you may be able to, for example, both enhance the use of Bright magic while also reduce damage taken from Dark magic. It is important to note resistances and damage buffs must match the damage type they are blocking or enhancing.{newline}
	{newline}Attack types
	{newline}Certain buffs and spells are only beneficial to certain attack types, which can include spell damage, melee damage or ranged damage. Only the benefits that match their attack type will be considered for the hit. {newline}
    {newline}Wardsave
	{newline}A special form of resistance is Wardsave. Wardsave acts last on the damage calculation, reducing the overall damage by a certain percentage. {newline}
	{newline}Damage calculation
	{newline}For a more detailed explanation of the damage calculation please head over to our Discord channel.{newline}
	 {newline}
	 {newline}
  " />
  
  <Concept title="{=!}Engineering" id="str_tor_engineeringgunpowder" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_ENGINEERING" text=
  "One of the major features of our mod is the use of artillery in battles. This is tied to the Engineering skill of players. Levelling your Engineering skill will allow you to acquire and use artillery on the battlefield. Once the player reaches 50 Engineering, they will able to purchase artillery from certain factions. Every 50 levels of Engineering allow the player to field an additional piece of artillery, up to maximum 6.{newline}
  {newline}The location or means of acquiring {TOR_ARTILLERY} will differ between each faction.{newline}
  {newline}
  " />
  <Concept title="{=!}Artillery" id="str_tor_artillery" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_ARTILLERY" text=
  "Cannons and Mortars
  {newline}The player can acquire Great Cannons and Mortars from the Imperial city of Nuln, after speaking to the Master Engineer NPC found in the city. Cannons and Mortars are only available to Imperial characters and have a number of requirements: to access the purchase screen alone a quest must first be completed, given by the Master Engineer.
  {newline}To buy and use Imperial artillery the player must have at least 50 Engineering, be part of an Imperial faction and have artillery crew in their party. Every additional 50 levels of Engineering allow the player to field an additional artillery piece.{newline}
  {newline}Field Trebuchets
  {newline}The player can acquire Field Trebuchets in Bretonnian towns with Wood Workshops by interacting with the trader.
  {newline}This powerful piece of artillery requires the player to have at least 50 Engineering. To properly operate Trebuchets infantry units need to be assigned to a placed artillery piece during the battle. Every additional 50 levels of Engineering allow the player to field an additional Trebuchet.{newline}
  {newline}
  {newline}
  " />
  
  <Concept title="{=!}Gunpowder" id="str_tor_guwpowder" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_GUNPOWDER" text=
  "One of our {TOR_ATTRIBUTES}, Gunpowder, is of course tied to the use of weapons like handguns. The player must use handguns or other blackpowder weapons in battles to level up their Gunpowder skill. Purchasing these weapons can be done by creating an Imperial character, hitting level 50 in Engineering and completing the quest given by the Master Engineer in Nuln. You can also buy them from traders in various cities.{newline}
  {newline}Finding and looting lower-quality guns or reading a Skill Book on Gunpowder is an excellent way to start this process early.
  {newline}
  " />
  
  <Concept title="{=!}Magic Introduction" id="str_tor_magic" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_MAGICINTRODUCTION" text=
  "Magic and Necromancy share many similar features - they can both be accessed by selecting relevant choices in the character creation or accessed by a non-magical character during a playthrough.{newline}
  {newline}
  To do this, the player must speak to a Magister/Dark Magister NPC and request a ‘magic test’, which will essentially ‘test’ the player's aptitude for the Winds of Magic and allow you to make use of magic from then onwards.{newline}
  {newline}
  Magic and Necromancy have tiers and progressions. To grow stronger and access stronger spells you must use magic in battles and then speak to the Magister NPC relevant to your faction: for Necromancers or Dark magic users that would be the Dark Magister whereas for Empire factions it would simply be Magister. They can be found in every Imperial or Sylvanian city.  
  {newline}
  Related Topics:{newline}
  {TOR_NECROMANCY}
  {TOR_MAGIC}
  {TOR_SPELLBOOK}
  {TOR_SPELLSELECTION}
  {TOR_ATTRIBUTES}
  {newline}
  "/>
  <Concept title="{=!}Magic" id="str_tor_magic" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_MAGIC" text=
  "To use magic in battle you simply have to, assuming the magic path was chosen, press Q (which can be remapped at your convenience). This will make your character enter spellcasting mode, providing you with an aiming reticule or an AoE outline, depending on the spell type. The player can scroll through his available spells by using the mouse wheel. The one you have selected at any given time is displayed at the bottom left of your screen.{newline} 
  {newline}We have also implemented our own ‘quick-cast’ system, which by default is the middle mouse button, and skips the aiming process when desired. What you can cast, as well as how often you can cast, is entirely dependent on your Winds of Magic resource (mana) and the individual cooldown of each spell. {newline}
  {newline}Winds of Magic
  {newline}All spells cost winds of Magic to cast. Winds of Magic are recharged by letting time pass on the campaign map. The current amount of Winds of Magic can be found in the lower right corner on the campaign map, and in the left corner during battles. In battle, this resource is depleted for every spell you cast.{newline}
  {newline}Lores of Magic
  {newline}The Old Realms currently features the following lores of magic:{newline}
  - Fire {newline}
  - Light {newline}
  - Dark {newline}
  - Necromancy {newline}
  - Heavens {newline}
  - Life {newline}
  - Beasts {newline}
 {newline}Players will have access to all of these, however, there are restrictions. Not every character can master multiple lores. Some Vampires can for example master Dark magic and Necromancy, whereas Damsels can master up to 3 lores. Based on certain {TOR_CAREERS}, races and the faction you join, the potential school selection and amount varies.  
 {newline}
 {newline}Each of these lores has its own progression with a range of unique spells, all of which are tied to our custom-made Spellcraft skill. Adding points in the Spellcraft skill raises your Winds of Magic capacity as well as its regeneration rate on the campaign map.{newline}
 {newline}
 {newline}
"
/>
  <Concept title="{=!}Necromancy" id="str_tor_necromancy" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_NECROMANCY" text=
  "Necromancy provides a custom feature for certain careers and races - the ability to raise the dead. Having access to these magics means that you will have the option to raise the dead after battles to bolster your armies, as well as visit specific locations (like {TOR_CURSEDLOCATIONS}) on the campaign map to recruit higher-tier undead units such as wraiths (see {TOR_RAISEDEAD}).{newline}
  "/>
  
  <Concept title="{=!}Spell Book" id="str_tor_spellbook" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_SPELLBOOK" text=
  "Spell Book can be accessed via the character screen and it stores all knowledge of magic, this includes companions in your party. In your spell book you can find information on the character's magic abilities such as their maximum Winds of Magic or mastered spells.{newline}
  {newline}All known and learnable spells are listed under their appropriate lore inside the spell book, which can be selected via the bookmark on the left side.{newline}
  {newline}Spell descriptions can be read by hovering the mouse cursor over the spells.
  "/>
  
  <Concept title="{=!}Spell Selection" id="str_tor_spellselection" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_SPELLSELECTION" text=
  "By clicking on the spells inside the {TOR_SPELLBOOK} you select them as combat spells, which will be usable the next time you enter a battle. All other spells will not be visible during the fight. If no spells are selected then all spells will be available to cast.{newline}" />
  
  <Concept title="{=!}Magic and Holy Items" id="str_tor_magicitems" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_MAGICITEMS" text=
  "Usually with a purple background, magic items come with a special effect, which can be read by hovering over the blue icon at the bottom of their tooltip. Those magic items often amplify the wearer’s magical abilities or offer additional protection. The player can acquire them by visiting vendors around the Old World or winning battles against the owners of such items.{newline}"/>
  
  <Concept title="{=!}Raise the Dead" id="str_tor_raise_dead" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_RAISEDEAD" text=
  "Certain characters and factions are able to raise the dead or offer characters the ability to become undead. The player can access this feature by playing as a necromancer or a Vampire. {newline}
  {newline}Post Battle Resurrection
  {newline}Based on your Discipline level (see {TOR_ATTRIBUTES}) there is a chance that every living creature that died in a battle will become a lesser undead warrior and join your army.{newline}
  {newline}Raiding Tombs
  {newline}As a necromancer you can also try your luck to resurrect undead in local graveyards, found as a new option within villages. Of course this has some risk, as most of the ‘good’ factions will immediately dislike you, furthermore if you choose to try and raise undead in towns or villages, you may be caught by the locals and will have to fight to survive. {newline}
  {newline}Priests and other careers are unable to perform Necromancy.
  {newline}
  " />
  
  <Concept title="{=!}New Attributes and Skills" id="str_tor_attributes" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_ATTRIBUTES" text=
  "Discipline is an attribute made specifically for TOR and it contains three new core skills.{newline}
  {newline}Gunpowder
  {newline}The Gunpowder skill accounts for weapons like pistols, handguns or even grenade-launching blunderbusses. To level up this skill, use gunpowder weapons or read Skill Books (see {TOR_SKILLBOOKS}) to obtain the minimal requirement for most guns. Characters and gunpowder units in the party will benefit from several perks and benefits directed to this new weapon type. Note that artillery pieces like Cannons are governed by the Engineering skill, not Gunpowder.{newline}
  {newline}Spellcraft
  {newline}The Spellcraft skill is exclusive to all characters able to perform magic. Several perks will increase the character's magic capabilities or his use of arcane knowledge. Skills are obtained via fighting with - and using magic in combat. New spells can be learned from Magister NPCs.{newline}
  {newline}Faith
  {newline}The Faith skill is exclusive to all believing peoples of the Old World - Necromancers and Vampires cannot level this skill. Faith can be increased by praying at a shrine (see {TOR_RELIGION}) or in the case of some specific careers, by performing prayers during battles. Faith increases the duration of blessings obtained from shrines. {newline}
  {newline}
  {newline}
  "/>
  
  <Concept title="{=!}Regiments of Renown" id="str_tor_ror" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_ROR" text=
  "Regiments of Renown (RoR) are unique factional troops that can only be recruited from specific locations and settlements on the campaign map, marked with a ‘RoR’ icon. Once you enter the settlement marked with ‘RoR’, there will be an option to select on the settlement menu.{newline}
  {newline}Those units cannot be recruited at the start. Instead, you must be a part of the appropriate faction and/or have reached a certain level of renown. Until these requirements have been met you will be refused recruitment of any Regiments of Renown.
  {newline}
  {newline}
  " />
  
  
  
  <Concept title="{=!}Religious Locations" id="str_tor_religion" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_RELIGION" text=
  "Around the world, players can find several locations where characters can receive blessings of various gods. Those blessings provide buffs for the whole party. Praying at a shrine can attract religious units like Flagellants or Battle Plgrims, which join the praying party. Note that the player as well as other lords can benefit from praying at a shrine. Additionally, your devotion for a god rises whenever you pray at a shrine.{newline}
  {newline}In the current update 3 religions are implemented and each provide their own unique blessings. {newline}
  {newline}Taal, the All-father of the human gods, patron of hunters, provides a movement buff when the party is travelling through forest terrain.{newline}
  {newline}Sigmar, the Uniter of mankind, provides a health regeneration buff for heroes in the party.{newline}
  {newline}The Lady of the Lake, the chief goddess of Bretonnia, provides a morale buff for all units within a party.{newline}
  {newline}Praying at a shrine is related to the Faith skill and higher Faith skill will prolong the blessing effect.
  {newline}New features can also be unlocked, like “donations” which allow the player to increase renown by donating items to a shrine.{newline}
  {newline}
  {newline}
  {newline}
  " />
  
  <Concept title="{=!}Skill Books" id="str_tor_skillbooks" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_SKILLBOOKS" text=
  "Skill books are another feature we have implmented alongside the Magister NPCs. Th Magisters will sell them and very similarily to Mount and Blade: Warband, you will passively read the book as you travel or rest. Skill Books grant skill experience when they are being read. Books are sold for a fair amount so they aren’t easily accessed from the start of the game. To read a book you must have it inside your inventory.
  {newline}
  {newline}Click on the book to reveal its description and a magnifying glass icon will appear in the lower right corner. If you have not already read that book, you will see a text notification stating that a book was selected for reading. If you already read that book, it will state that you are already familiar with this book. When time passes (by travelling or resting) you will read the contents of the book and your appropriate skill will increase. No book can be read twice.{newline}
  {newline}
  {newline}
  " />
  
  
  
  <Concept title="{=!}Vampire" id="str_tor_vampire" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_VAMPIRE" text=
  "To start the game as a Vampire, you must choose the ‘Vampire nobility’ option during character creation. When you load onto the campaign map your character will have the appearance and powers of a Vampire, such as access to magic, Necromancy and other abilities planned for the future.{newline}
  {newline}If you wish to become a Vampire after starting the game as a regular human, join the Vampire Counts and speak to Mannfred Von Carstein once you have sufficient renown and relations. Alternatively, you have to be part of the Order of the Blood Dragon, and ask Walach Harkon to become a Blood Knight. Doing so will provide an option to ‘receive the Blood Kiss’ which will then change your character into a Vampire and replace your career with the Blood Knight or Vampire Noble.
  {newline}
  {newline}Vampires learn new magic through Dark Magister NPCs found in settlements, similar to standard magic users.{newline}
  {newline}
  {newline}
  " />
  
  <Concept title="{=!}Priests and Prayers" id="str_tor_prayers" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_PRAYERS" text=
  "Priest Careers and Prayers
  {newline}Starting as the Priest Acolyte, or the Damsel of the Lady, will make the player representative of the beliefs in the Old World. They are the only careers and peoples that have access to prayers or battle prayers.{newline}
  {newline}Other than spells, prayers are directly unlocked upon reaching a certain skill level of the Faith skill. Starting with the adept skill at the “Novice Prayer” prayer perk up to the “Grand prayer” perk at skill 125, new prayers will be unlocked. Non Priest career types, cannot unlock any prayers for combat but can receive the blessings from {TOR_RELIGION}. {newline}
  {newline}Prayers have no cost and can be quite powerful. To make these abilities balanced, the cooldown is shared across all prayers and it is fairly long. Addionally prayers are not available to cast at the battle start. Naturally, Vampires and necromancers don't get access to prayers.{newline}
  {newline}In the current update the following prayers are available:{newline}
  {newline}Sigmar
  {newline}- Healing Hand: Troops inside the area get healed for 5 health points per second for a total duration of 9 seconds.
  {newline}- Armour of the Righteous: Allies in a 3 meter radius gain 35% physical resistance for 8 seconds.
  {newline}- Vanquish: Allies in a target radius gain the burning weapon trait that ignites enemies and deals fire damage.
  {newline}- Comet of Sigmar: A projectile is launched at the enemy, dealing about 30 holy damage. The explosion can knock down enemies and dismount riders.{newline}
  {newline}
  {newline}Lady of the Lake
  {newline}- Aura of the Lady: Provides 80% reduction from magic, fire and lightning to allies in the area.
  {newline}- Shield Of Combat: Adds 40% physical resistance against ranged damage for 15 seconds to the caster and surrounding friendly units.
  {newline}- Lady's Favour: Increases attack speed of allied units inside the area by 25%.
  {newline}- Aerial Shield: Completely protects allies inside the area from ranged damage.
  {newline}
  {newline}
  {newline}
  " />
  
  <Concept title="{=!}Text adventures" id="str_tor_text_adventures" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_TEXTADVENTURES" text=
  "
  From time to time while travelling through the world, events can occur that need the action of the player. During those events, the game can’t be saved and the story has to be finished before the game continues. {newline}
  {newline}
  Based on character skills and other attributes, like being a Necromancer or Vampire, the choices and approaches in the situation differ, and the chance of a positive outcome varies. The outcome of those events can affect the world.{newline}
  {newline}
  These events are triggered randomly and are sometimes based on situations and the surroundings of the player. {newline}
  {newline}
  {newline}
  " />
  
  <Concept title="{=!}Special Mounts" id="str_tor_text_adventures" group="The Old Realms" link_id="TOR_TEXTADVENTURES" text=
  "The Old World is a home to many extraordinary creatures, some of which can also act as powerful mounts.
  {newline}As of now, our mod features only three such creatures: the majestic Demigryphs of the Empire, Zombie Horses and spectral Ghost Horses of the Vampire Counts.{newline}
  {newline}At this point Zombie and Ghost Horses can be bought from traders and Demigryphs can only be acquired as rare battle loot. There are plans to implement specific quests which would award the player with these mounts.{newline}
  {newline}
  {newline}
  " />
  
</Concepts>
